http://www.drpeter.org/footer/legal/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
SHARE
The Dr. Peter AIDS Foundation protects the privacy of the information that you share with us. The information you provide will be used to provide tax receipts, to contact you regarding donations &/or event ticket purchases, and to keep you informed of Dr. Peter AIDS Foundation news and activities.
The Dr. Peter AIDS Foundation protects your personal information with appropriate security safeguards, including physical, administrative, and electronic security measures.
Website
We do not use cookies to track users who are visiting our website. Aggregate information (number of overall visitors, peak traffic times, most visited sections, etc.) from our website is recorded; however, this information is not connected to individual user sessions.
Disclosure of Information to Third Parties
Under no circumstances will the Dr. Peter AIDS Foundation sell, trade, or rent your personal information to third parties.
The Dr. Peter AIDS Foundation contracts services such as online donation processing and email distribution to third party organizations. In such cases, the Dr. Peter AIDS Foundation maintains ownership of the data and ensures appropriate security undertakings, such as confidentiality clauses in contractual agreements, are employed to protect the transfer and use of personal information.
Canada Revenue Agency Requirements Relating to Donations
In order to satisfy the requirements of the Canada Revenue Agency, the Dr. Peter AIDS Foundation maintains records of all receipted contributions. All personal information is private and confidential. Refunds will be issued on a case by case basis.
If you have any questions or concerns regarding the Dr. Peter AIDS Foundation’s Privacy Policy, please contact 604.608.1874 or privacyofficer@drpeter.org
Get connected:
HIV TODAY
Learn More
Make a quick donation here
Donate Today
